<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Sesh</string>
    <string name="title_activity_login">LoginActivity</string>
    <string name="title_splash">SplashActivity</string>

    <string name="facebook_app_id">905781159496730</string>

    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="title_activity_home">Home</string>
    <string name="title_activity_profile">Profile</string>
    <string name="title_activity_payment">Payment</string>
    <string name="title_activity_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="title_activity_promote">Promote</string>
    <string name="title_activity_in_sesh">In Sesh</string>

    <string name="major_hint">Tell us a bit about yourself!</string>

    <string name="learn_tab_button_title">LEARN</string>
    <string name="teach_tab_button_title">TEACH</string>
    <string name="title_activity_maps">Map</string>
    <string name="terms_label">By creating an account you agree to the Terms Of Use and you acknowledge that you have read the Privacy Policy.</string>
    <string name="email_sent_title">EMAIL SENT!</string>
    <string name="confirmation_code_activity_text">We\'ve sent you an email to verify your account.  Once you\'ve clicked the link, you will be automatically taken to profile setup! Almost there!</string>
    <string name="title_activity_change_password">ChangePasswordActivity</string>

    <string name="hello_world">Hello world!</string>
    <string name="title_activity_about">AboutActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_terms">TermsActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_privacy">PrivacyActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_support">SupportActivity</string>

    <string name="messaging_activity">MessagingActivity</string>

    <string name="student_report_problem">Providing great tutors is our number one concern. Please let us know about any problems you may have experienced during your Sesh. Your comments will not be seen by the tutor.</string>
    <string name="tutor_report_problem">We value our tutors and want to continue to improve your experience. Please let us know about any problems you may have experienced during your Sesh. Your comments will not be seen by the student.</string>

    <string name="view_classes_on_text">close to view available jobs</string>
    <string name="view_classes_off_text">tap to view eligible courses</string>

    <string name="support_url">https://seshtutoring.com/faq</string>

    <string name="payment_agreement">By inserting your card information you are agreeing to the Sesh Terms and Conditions and understand that Sesh is a marketplace and not a courier company. We will not charge your credit card until you successfully complete a tutoring session.</string>

    <string name="affirmative">YES!</string>
    <string name="negative">NO</string>
    <string name="cashout_dialog">Would you like to cash out your tutor credits? The transfer will take 1-2 days to complete.</string>

    <string name="terms_of_use">
        TERMS AND CONDITIONS\n
The terms and conditions stated herein (collectively, the Agreement) constitute a legal agreement between you (the user) and Vanford Inc., a Delaware corporation (the Company).  This Agreement sets forth the terms and governs your use of the Sesh Tutoring Application (Sesh or the Application).  By creating a Sesh account and/or by downloading the mobile application, you agree to be bound by these terms.\n
There are two types of Application users: student-users and tutor-users.  Sesh is a service that connects student-users with tutor-users.  Tutor-users will have knowledge of the subject areas in which the student-users need help.  The determination that a tutor-user has knowledge of as subject area will be based only upon review of the tutor-users transcript.  All users, student-users and tutor-users, must read and agree to these terms and conditions.  Your use of the Application as either a student-user or a tutor-user will be additional evidence of your agreement to these terms.\n
Your use of the Application is licensed only on the condition that you agree to the terms and conditions set forth below. PLEASE READ THE TERMS OF THIS AGREEMENT CAREFULLY.\n
The Company reserves the right to modify this Agreement or its policies relating to the Application at any time.  You are responsible for regularly reviewing this Agreement.  Continued use of the Application after any such changes shall constitute your consent to such changes.\n
Access to and use of the Application is by permission of the Company only, and only for users who accept this Agreement. The Company may grant or withhold access to the Application and may terminate your account in its sole discretion.
Based on the foregoing and for other good and valuable consideration, you and Company agree as follows:\n\n

1.  Definitions.\n
Users.  Student-users are students currently enrolled at a United States college or university with a valid .edu email address.  Student-users will designate that they wish to use the Application as a student-user.  Tutor-users are students currently enrolled at a United States college or university with a valid .edu email address.  Tutor-users will designate that they wish to use the Application as a tutor-user and must separately apply to be a tutor-user with the Company.  As part of the application process, tutor-users must provide a valid and current transcript.  Tutor-users will be required to enter into a consulting agreement with the Company.\n
Account.  Along with agreeing to these terms and conditions, all users must provide the Company with certain identifying information, including your name and .edu email address.  All users must have a valid Account that will allow you to access the Application.
Account Information.  The information collected and stored by the Company regarding each user.  A users Account Information will provide the user access to the Application and allow the Company to identify the user.  Account Information will be collected when the user signs up and additional information may be requested by the Company as necessary.\n
Sesh Application.  The Application facilitates the connection of tutor-users and student-users.  Student-users may enter information related to tutoring services or homework help that the student-user needs.  Tutor-users may access information related to student-user needs and set up a tutoring session.  The Application provides a messaging system that may be used by student-users and tutor-users to schedule tutoring sessions and communicate.\n
2.  License Grant.  Under this Agreement, the Company grants to you a nonexclusive, nonassignable, nonsublicensable license, for your internal use only, for the term of this Agreement, to access and use the Application and any users guides, specifications, and other related documentation available online (the Documentation), subject to the terms and conditions of this Agreement.\n
3.  Requirements for Users.  All users must be 18-years old or older.  All users must be enrolled in a United States college or university and have a current and valid .edu email address.\n
4.  Ownership of Application.  Company retains all rights to the Application and the Documentation not specifically granted in this Agreement. The Company owns the Application and the Documentation and all copyright and other intellectual property rights contained within them, and this Agreement does not transfer to you any title to or any proprietary or intellectual property rights in or to the Application, any updates or derivative works to them, or the Documentation, or any copyrights, patent rights, or trademarks embodied or used in connection with them, except for the rights expressly granted in this Agreement. The Application and the Documentation are protected by United States laws and international treaty provisions.\n
YOU MAY NOT USE, COPY, OR MODIFY THE APPLICATION, IN WHOLE OR IN PART, EXCEPT AS EXPRESSLY PROVIDED FOR IN THIS AGREEMENT.\n
5.  Restrictions.  To the maximum extent permitted by law, you shall not (a) modify, reverse engineer, decompile, disassemble, or attempt to derive the source code of the Application; (b) rent, lease, loan, sell, sublicense, distribute, transmit, or otherwise transfer the Application access to any third party; (c) make any copy of or otherwise reproduce the Application (or any of the browser screens comprising the Application user interface) except for copies necessarily made by the personal computer and Internet browser that are running the Application; or (d) use the Application to provide service bureau or time-sharing services; or (e) disclose your Account Information to any third party.\n
You agree to take all reasonable steps to safeguard your Account Information to ensure that no unauthorized person will have access to it, and that no persons authorized to have access will make any unauthorized use. You shall promptly report to Company any unauthorized use of the Application of which you become aware and shall take such further steps as may reasonably be requested by Company to prevent unauthorized use of the Application.\n
6.  Your Obligations.  You are solely responsible for the following: (a) providing all hardware, software, and communications capabilities required for use of the Application; (b) generating, providing, and loading your data into the Application; and (c) providing and maintaining, at all times during the term of this Agreement, the Internet access necessary for your use of the Application.\n
7.  Payment.  Student-users and Tutor-users must sign-up with a third party payment system for payment processing.  Student-users and tutor-users will be prompted to sign-up with a payment processor prior to scheduling any tutoring sessions.  Payment is due immediately after the conclusion of a tutoring session.  Payment is subject to rates specified by the Company and determined at the time the tutoring session is requested.  Rates may be based on the time of day, location, and subject-matter of the tutoring session. \n
8.  Term And Termination.  The license granted in this Agreement is effective until terminated. The term of this Agreement and the license grant under it will commence on the date you agree to this Agreement. You may terminate the license and this Agreement at any time. Company may terminate the license and this Agreement at any time on written notice to you that you or your agent has failed to pay any amount due to Company under this Agreement. This license also terminates automatically on your failure to comply with any of the other terms of this Agreement. On termination of this Agreement, you will no longer be able to access your account.\n
9.  Confidentiality.  You agree that you shall not disclose to any third party the Application or any portion of it, any technical, product, or business information, or any information that Company identifies as confidential (collectively, Confidential Information) related to the Application without the prior written consent of Company. You shall maintain the confidentiality of all Confidential Information and shall not use it for any purpose other than the performance of this Agreement.\n
Notwithstanding the foregoing, Confidential Information does not include information that you can demonstrate was (a) publicly available at the time of disclosure, or later became publicly available through no act or omission by you; (b) in your possession before disclosure by Company; or (c) disclosed to you by a third party not in violation of any obligations of confidentiality to Company or to any third party.\n
10.  Indemnification.  By entering into this Agreement and using the Application, you agree that you shall defend, indemnify and hold the Company, its licensors and each such partys parent organizations, subsidiaries, affiliates, officers, directors, users, employees, attorneys and agents harmless from and against any and all claims, costs, damages, losses, liabilities and expenses (including attorneys fees and costs) arising out of or in connection with: (a) your violation or breach of any term of this Agreement or any applicable law or regulation, whether or not referenced herein; (b) your violation of any rights of any third party, including providers of tutoring services arranged via the Application; or (c) your use or misuse of the Application.\n
11.  Limitation of Liability.  You are not entitled to receive damages from Company for any cause relating to this Agreement, to your use of the Application, to any services provided by the Company under this Agreement, or to any services provided by any third party in connection with your use of the Application. In addition, in no event will you be entitled to obtain any injunctive relief or enjoin, restrain, or otherwise interfere with the Company or with the distribution, operation, development, or performance of the Application or any related products.\n
IN NO EVENT WILL THE COMPANY BE LIABLE TO YOU FOR ANY DAMAGES WHATSOEVER ARISING OUT OF YOUR USE OF, OR INABILITY TO USE, THE APPLICATION. IN NO EVENT WILL THE COMPANY BE LIABLE FOR ANY SPECIAL, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES, OR DAMAGES FOR LOSS OF DATA, LOST PROFITS, OR LOST BUSINESS OPPORTUNITIES, REGARDLESS OF THE LEGAL THEORY UNDER WHICH SUCH DAMAGES ARE SOUGHT, AND EVEN IF ADVISED IN ADVANCE OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES. AS SOME STATES DO NOT ALLOW THE LIMITATION OR EXCLUSION OF LIABILITY FOR INCIDENTAL OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES, THE ABOVE LIMITATION OR EXCLUSION MAY NOT APPLY TO YOU.\n
THE COMPANY OFFERS USERS THE OPPORTUNITY TO MEET OTHER USERS FOR THE PURPOSES OF RECEIVING OR PROVIDING TUTORING SERVICES.  WE WILL NOT ASSESS THE SUITABILITY, LEGALITY OR ABILITY OF ANY TUTOR-USER AND YOU EXPRESSLY WAIVE AND RELEASE THE COMPANY FROM ANY AND ALL LIABILITY, CLAIMS OR DAMAGES ARISING FROM OR IN ANY WAY RELATED TO ANY OTHER USER.  YOU ACKNOWLEDGE THAT TUTORS REQUESTED THROUGH THE APPLICATION MAY NOT BE CERTIFIED OR HAVE PRIOR TUTORING EXPERIENCE.  THE COMPANY WILL NOT BE A PARTY TO DISPUTES, NEGOTIATIONS OF DISPUTES BETWEEN YOU AND ANY OTHER USER.  RESPONSIBILITY FOR THE DECISIONS YOU MAKE REGARDING SERVICES OFFERED VIA THE APPLICATION RESTS SOLELY WITH YOU.  WE WILL NOT ASSES THE SUITABILITY, LEGALITY OR ABILITY OF ANY SUCH THIRD PARTIES AND YOU EXPRESSLY WAIVE AND RELEASE THE COMPANY FROM ANY AND ALL LIABILITY, CLAIMS, CAUSES OF ACTION, OR DAMAGES ARISING FROM YOUR USE OF THE APPLICATION OR SERVICE, OR IN ANY WAY RELATED TO THE THIRD PARTIES INTRODUCED TO YOU BY THE APPLICATION.  YOU EXPRESSLY WAIVE AND RELEASE ANY AND ALL RIGHTS AND BENEFITS UNDER SECTION 1542 OF THE CIVIL CODE OF THE STATE OF CALIFORNIA (OR ANY ANALOGOUS LAW OF ANY OTHER STATE), WHICH READS AS FOLLOWS: A GENERAL RELEASE DOES NOT EXTEND TO CLAIMS WHICH THE CREDITOR DOES NOT KNOW OR SUSPECT TO EXIST IN HIS FAVOR AT THE TIME OF EXECUTING THE RELEASE, WHICH, IF KNOWN BY HIM, MUST HAVE MATERIALLY AFFECTED HIS SETTLEMENT WITH THE DEBTOR.\n
THE QUALITY OF THE TUTORING SERVICES SCHEDULED THROUGH THE USE OF THE APPLICATION IS ENTIRELY THE RESPONSIBILITY OF THE USER- TUTOR.  YOU UNDERSTAND, THEREFORE, THAT BY USING THE APPLICATION YOU MAY BE EXPOSED TO SITUATIONS THAT ARE POTENTIALLY DANGEROUS, OFFENSIVE, HARMFUL TO MINORS, UNSAFE OR OTHERWISE OBJECTIONABLE, AND THAT YOU USE THE APPLICATION AND THE SERVICE AT YOUR OWN RISK.\n
DISCLAIMER OF WARRANTIES\n
THE COMPANY MAKES NO REPRESENTATION, WARRANTY, OR GUARANTY AS TO THE RELIABILITY, TIMELINESS, QUALITY, SUITABILITY, AVAILABILITY, ACCURACY OR COMPLETENESS OF THE APPLICATION.  THE COMPANY DOES NOT REPRESENT OR WARRANT THAT (A) YOUR USE OF THE APPLICATION WILL BE SECURE, TIMELY, UNINTERRUPTED OR ERROR-FREE OR OPERATE IN COMBINATION WITH ANY OTHER HARDWARE, APPLICATION, SYSTEM OR DATA, (B) THE APPLICATION WILL MEET YOUR REQUIREMENTS OR EXPECTATIONS, (C) ANY STORED DATA WILL BE ACCURATE OR RELIABLE, (D) THE QUALITY OF ANY PRODUCTS, SERVICES, INFORMATION, OR OTHER MATERIAL PURCHASED OR OBTAINED BY YOU THROUGH THE APPLICATION WILL MEET YOUR REQUIREMENTS OR EXPECTATIONS, (E) ERRORS OR DEFECTS IN THE APPLICATION WILL BE CORRECTED, OR (F) THE APPLICATION OR THE SERVER(S) THAT MAKE THE APPLICATION AVAILABLE ARE FREE OF VIRUSES OR OTHER HARMFUL COMPONENTS.  THE APPLICATION IS PROVIDED TO YOU STRICTLY ON AN AS IS BASIS.\n
TO THE MAXIMUM EXTENT PERMITTED BY LAW, THE COMPANY EXPRESSLY DISCLAIMS ANY AND ALL WARRANTIES, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY AND FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE, AS WELL AS ANY WARRANTIES ALLEGED TO HAVE ARISEN FROM CUSTOM, USAGE, OR THE COURSE OF DEALING BETWEEN THE PARTIES. THE COMPANY DOES NOT WARRANT THAT THE FUNCTIONS CONTAINED IN THE APPLICATION WILL MEET YOUR REQUIREMENTS OR THAT THE OPERATION OF THE APPLICATION WILL BE UNINTERRUPTED OR ERROR-FREE. IN ADDITION, THE COMPANY DOES NOT WARRANT OR GUARANTEE THAT YOU WILL BE ABLE TO ACCESS THE APPLICATION AT ALL TIMES. YOU UNDERSTAND AND ACKNOWLEDGE THAT INTERNET CONGESTION AND OUTAGES, AS WELL AS MAINTENANCE, DOWNTIME, AND OTHER INTERRUPTIONS, MAY INTERFERE AT TIMES WITH YOUR ABILITY TO ACCESS THE APPLICATION.\n
12.  Governing Law.  This Agreement is governed by and construed in accordance with the laws of the State of California, without regard to its conflict of laws provisions.\n
13.  Force Majeure.  If the performance of Company under this Agreement is prevented, hindered, or otherwise made impractical because of flood, strike, war, acts of government, or any other casualty or cause beyond the control of Company, then Company will be excused from its performance to the extent and as long as it is prevented, hindered, or delayed by any of these events.\n
14.  Severability.  If any one or more of the provisions contained in this Agreement is, for any reason, held to be invalid, illegal, or unenforceable in any respect, then to the maximum extent permitted by law, the invalidity, illegality, or unenforceability will not affect any other provision of this Agreement.\n
15.  No Assignment.  You may not assign this Agreement or any of the rights granted by Company under it, in whole or in part, without the prior written consent of Company, and any attempt to do so is a breach of this Agreement. This Agreement is binding on and inures to the benefit of the parties and their respective successors and permitted assigns.\n
16.  Export Control.  You agree to obey and comply with all applicable United States laws, rules, and regulations governing the export of software.\n
17.  Acknowledgment And Exclusivity.  YOU ACKNOWLEDGE THAT YOU HAVE READ THIS AGREEMENT, UNDERSTAND IT, AND AGREE TO BE BOUND BY ITS TERMS AND CONDITIONS. YOU FURTHER AGREE THAT IT IS THE COMPLETE AND EXCLUSIVE STATEMENT OF THE AGREEMENT BETWEEN YOU AND THE COMPANY, AND THAT IT SUPERSEDES ANY PROPOSAL, PRIOR AGREEMENT, OR UNDERSTANDING, ORAL OR WRITTEN, AND ANY OTHER COMMUNICATION BETWEEN YOU AND THE COMPANY RELATING TO THE SUBJECT MATTER OF THIS AGREEMENT.\n
    </string>

    <string name="privacy_policy">
PRIVACY POLICY\n
Sesh is dedicated to protecting Your personal information and informing You about how We use it. This privacy policy applies to transactions and activities and data gathered through the Sesh Application. Please review this privacy policy periodically as We may revise it without notice. This privacy policy was last revised onDecember 15, 2014. Each time You use the Sesh Application or provide Us with information, by doing so You are accepting the practices described in this privacy policy at that time.
\n\n
DATA WE COLLECT FROM YOU\n
In order to operate the Sesh Application and to provide You with information about products or services that may be of interest to You, We may collect personal information (i.e. information that could be used to contact You directly (without using the Sesh Application) such as full name, postal address, phone number, credit/debit card information, or email address) or demographic information (i.e. information that You submit, or that We collect, that is not personal information; this may include, but is not limited to, zip code, hometown, gender, username, age/birth date, browsing history information, searching history information, and registration history information). We will also collect the contact information of Your friends, if You choose to connect Your contacts and address book information with Sesh and Your login credentials to Your social network accounts, such as Facebook and Twitter, if You choose to connect those accounts with your Sesh account. You represent and warrant that You have the authority to provide Us with any such contact information. Demographic information is divided into two categories:
1. non-public information, which consists of ride transaction information and one-on-one communications between You and other users of the Sesh Application; and
2. public information, which consists of all other demographic information.
Please note that nowhere on the Sesh Application do We knowingly collect, keep or maintain personal information from children under the age of 18, as We require that all users represent to Us that they are at least 18 years old.
\n\n
HOW WE USE PERSONAL INFORMATION\n
We use Your email address and Your other personal information to help Us efficiently operate the Sesh Application, to contact You in connection with Your transactions and other activities on the Sesh Application (including, but not limited to, confirmation emails, or important news that could affect Your relationship with Sesh), to forward tutoring information to You from other Users, to forward tutoring information from You to other Users, and to contact You and others to suggest potential matches. We use Your contact information to find and connect with Your friends (when instructed by You). These types of communications are known as Operational Communications. In some cases, Operational Communications may also contain commercial messages, such as banner ads and special offers.
To operate the Sesh Application, including processing Your transactions and supporting Your activities on the Sesh Application, We may share Your personal information with Our agents, representatives, contractors and service providers so they can provide Us with support services such as email origination, receipt or support services, customer relationship management services, and order fulfillment. We require these entities not to use Your information for any other purpose.
By purchasing, or registering or making reservations for, products or services offered or sponsored by third parties on the Sesh Application, or electing to receive communications (such as emails or material by mail) or electing to participate in contests, sweepstakes or other programs (such as discount or rewards programs), offered or sponsored by third parties on the Sesh Application, You consent to Our providing Your personal information to those third parties. Those third parties may use Your personal information in accordance with their own privacy policies. You will need to contact those third parties to instruct them directly regarding Your preferences for the use of Your personal information by them. Additionally, You agree that We may use and disclose all such information so submitted to such third parties in the same manner in which We are entitled to use and disclose any other information You submit to Us.
Any third party with whom We are allowed to share Your personal information is authorized to use Your personal information in accordance with Our contractual arrangements with such third parties and in accordance with their own privacy policies, over which We have no control, and You agree that We are not responsible or liable for any of their actions or omissions. Those who contact You will need to be instructed directly by You regarding Your preferences for the use of Your personal information by them.
\n\n
HOW WE USE DEMOGRAPHIC DATA\n
We may review all demographic Data. We may use public information to enable other users to search Your profile, to determine whether Your tutoring details fit other user\'s requirements, and to communicate with You. We may use demographic information to tailor the Sesh Application and communications to Your interests. We may also share demographic information with advertisers on an anonymous and aggregated basis (i.e., without telling the advertisers Your identity). One of the reasons We may do this is to increase the likelihood that Our advertisers\' goods and services will appeal to You as a user of the Sesh Application. Our sharing of demographic information with advertisers is anonymous (i.e., We do not tell advertisers which particular Sesh Users are members of which demographic groups), subject to the rest of this privacy policy. When You respond to an advertisement, however, We ask You to remember that if that ad that is targeted to a demographic group and You decide to give the advertiser Your personal information, then the advertiser may be able to identify You as being a member of that demographic group.
\n\n
HOW TO EDIT YOUR INFORMATION\n
Sesh provides You with the ability to access and edit Your personal information. To update Your personal info, click Profile in the Sesh menu. There You can view, update and correct Your account information.
So that We can protect the integrity of sensitive data, there are certain pieces of information, such as Your age, that You cannot alter Yourself.
Our databases automatically update any personal information You edit in Your profile, or that You request We edit. Information transmitted through boards, chats, polls or through any other means remain in Our databases and become the property of Sesh upon submission. Keep this in mind if You decide to communicate personal information through any of these applications.
\n\n
INFORMATION RETENTION\n
To preserve the integrity of Our databases, standard procedure calls for Us to retain information submitted by members for an indefinite length of time. Sesh understands Your submissions as consent to store all Your information in one place for this indefinite length of time, if We so wish. If required by law, as is the case to comply with the Children\'s Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA), We will nullify member information by erasing it from Our database. We will also respond to written member requests to nullify account information. Also, by using the Sesh Application, You do hereby represent and warrant that You understand and agree that all information submitted by You through the Sesh Application or otherwise to Sesh becomes the property of Sesh and may be used in the sole discretion of Sesh in accordance with this Privacy Policy and the Terms of Use.
\n\n
CHOICE/OPT-OUT\n
Sesh provides Users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from Us and Our partners at the point where We request information about the visitor. Sesh gives Users the option to remove their information from Our database, to not receive future communications or to no longer receive Our service.
\n\n
SPECIAL CASES IN WHICH WE SHARE PERSONAL INFORMATION\n
Your personal information may be passed on to a third party in the event of a transfer of ownership or assets, or a bankruptcy. We may also disclose personal information when We determine that such disclosure is necessary to comply with applicable law, to cooperate with law enforcement or to protect the interests or safety of Sesh or other visitors to the Sesh Application. We also may disclose Your personal information to Our subsidiary and parent companies and businesses, and other affiliated legal entities and businesses with whom We are under common corporate control. Whenever personal information is disclosed under this paragraph, We may also disclose Your demographic information along with it, on a non-anonymous basis. All of Our parent, subsidiary and affiliated legal entities and businesses that receive Your personal information or non-anonymous demographic information from Us will comply with the terms of this privacy policy with respect to their use and disclosure of such information.
\n\n
OUR SECURITY PRECAUTIONS\n
Your Sesh Profile is password-protected so that only You and authorized Sesh employees have access to Your account information. In order to maintain this protection, do not give Your password to anyone. Sesh staff will never proactively reach out to You and ask for any personal account information, including Your password. If You share a computer, You should sign out of Your Sesh account and close the browser window before someone else logs on. This will help protect Your information entered on public terminals from disclosure to third parties.
Sesh makes every effort to ensure that Your information is secure on its system. Sesh has staff dedicated to maintaining Our privacy policy as set forth herein and other privacy initiatives, periodically reviewing Web security and making sure that every Sesh employee is aware of Our security practices. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, Sesh cannot guarantee the security of any information You transmit to Us, and You do so at Your own risk. If You have any further questions on this issue, refer to Sesh Terms of Use. Sesh expressly disclaims any liability that may arise should any other individuals obtain the information You submit to the Sesh Application.
Sesh has security measures in place to protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under Our control. Your information may be transferred to and maintained on computer networks which may be located outside of the state, province, country or other governmental jurisdiction in which You reside, and the country or jurisdiction in which these computer networks are located may not have privacy laws as protective as the laws in Your country or jurisdiction.
The Sesh Application may contain links to other web sites. We are of course not responsible for the privacy practices of other web sites. We encourage Our Users to be aware when they leave the Sesh Application to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This Privacy Policy applies solely to information collected by the Sesh Application.
\n\n
CHANGING OUR PRIVACY POLICY FOR PREVIOUSLY GATHERED INFORMATION\n
If at any point We decide to use particular personally identifiable information in a manner materially different from that stated at the time it was collected, We will notify Users by way of an email or by providing 30 days notice on the Sesh Application. We also encourage You to review this privacy policy periodically. By using the Sesh Application, You do hereby represent and warrant that You have read, understand and agree to all terms of Agreement. Each time You use the Sesh Application, You agree to all terms set forth in this Agreement and any other policies published by Sesh on the Sesh Application. Please note that We will continue to have the right to change Our privacy policy and practices, and how We use Your personally identifiable information, without notice, as described in herein, provided that such changes shall only apply to information gathered on or after the date of the change.
\n\n
CONTACTING SESH\n
If You have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of Sesh, or Your dealings with Sesh, You may contact Us at team@seshtutoring.com
    </string>

    <string name="number_of_students_text">How many students will be taking part in you Sesh?</string>
    <string name="number_of_students_charge_text">$5 per extra student per hour</string>
    <string name="per_minute_rate">$0.42/min</string>
    <string name="end_early_reminder">*Remember, you can end early if you want. (Min. 30 minutes)</string>
    <string name="review_details_text">Always check your answers!  Review the details for your upcoming Sesh.</string>
    <string name="title_activity_add_card">AddCard</string>
    <string name="end_sesh_button">End Sesh</string>

<!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>

    <string name="first_fragment_title">Welcome</string>
    <string name="first_fragment_content">Sesh is a mobile peer-to-peer tutoring marketplace for college students looking to learn and earn at the tap of a button.</string>

    <string name="second_fragment_title">Students</string>
    <string name="second_fragment_content">Get help with assignments any time, any place.  Tutors who\'ve taken the class before will come directly to you.</string>

    <string name="third_fragment_title">Tutors</string>
    <string name="third_fragment_content">Sign up to tutor on your campus and start earning cash on your own schedule.</string>


    <string name="fourth_fragment_content">We are constantly working to bring you the best experience possible. Be excited about future updates, and enjoy earning and learning with Sesh. Tap below to begin your journey!</string>

    <string name="update_app_dialog_content">Please update Sesh now to start learning and earning today!  Sesh cannot run unless the update is installed.  Happy Seshing!</string>

    <string name="unreleased_launch_thank_you">Thank you for signing up for Sesh.  We can\'t wait to get you started!</string>
    <string name="unreleased_launch_content">The Sesh Team is hard at work putting the final touches on our Android app -- we\'ll be sure to notify you as soon as the app is ready.</string>

    <string name="sesh_created_tutor_dialog_title">You got the Job!</string>
    <string name="sesh_created_student_dialog_title">You got a Tutor!</string>
    <string name="sesh_created_tutor_dialog_text">Time to save %1$s\'s day!  Please confirm your meeting location and start time with %1$s.  You can message within the app.</string>
    <string name="sesh_created_student_dialog_text">%1$s picked up your request!  Please confirm your meeting location and start time with %1$s.  You can message within the app.</string>

    <string name="sesh_request_timeout_dialog_text">We could not find you a tutor for %1$s right now.  Would you like us to keep looking?  For how long?</string>
    <string name="title_activity_view_sesh_set_time">ViewSeshSetTimeActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_view_sesh_map">ViewSeshMapActivity</string>

    <string name="learn_request_time_early_end_label">*Remember, you can end the Sesh early if you want. (Min. 30 minutes)</string>
    <string name="title_activity_tutor_terms">TutorTermsActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_add_tutor_classes">AddTutorClassesActivity</string>

    <string name="drawer_layout_open">open</string>
    <string name="drawer_layout_close">close</string>
</resources>
